<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Final_Project</string>
    <string name="Harry1">It is a story about Harry Potter, an orphan brought up by his aunt and uncle because his parents were killed when he was a baby. Harry is unloved by his uncle and aunt but everything changes when he is invited to join Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.</string>
    <string name="Harry2">The second instalment of boy wizard Harry Potters adventures at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, based on the novel by JK Rowling. A mysterious elf tells Harry to expect trouble during his second year at Hogwarts.</string>
    <string name="Harry3">a young wizard, in his third year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Along with friends Ronald Weasley and Hermione Granger, Harry investigates Sirius Black,an escaped prisoner from Azkaba, believed to be one of Lord Voldemorts old allies.</string>
    <string name="Hunger1">The Hunger Games is a 2008 dystopian novel by the American writer Suzanne Collins. It is written in the voice of 16-year-old Katniss Everdeen, who lives in the future, post-apocalyptic nation of Panem in North America. The Capitol.</string>
    <string name="Hunger2">After arriving safely home from their unprecedented victory in the 74th Annual Hunger Games, Katniss Everdeen (Jennifer Lawrence) and Peeta Mellark (Josh Hutcherson) discover that they must do a quick turnaround and begin a Victors Tour.</string>
    <string name="it">In 1960, seven preteen outcasts fight an evil demon that poses as a child-killing clown. Thirty years later, they reunite to stop the demon once and for all when it returns to their hometown.</string>
    <string name="Shinging">The Shining centers on the life of Jack Torrance, a struggling writer and recovering alcoholic who accepts a position as the off-season caretaker of the historic Overlook Hotel in the Colorado Rockies.</string>
    <string name="pet">The story of Pet Sematary follows husband and wife Luis and Rachel Creed who relocate their family from Boston to rural Maine. In the book, the Creed family relocate from Chicago. Along with their two children, the couple moves into a house with a burial ground in the woods near their home.</string>

</resources>